Guide to the Lindseth Collection of Alice Ephemera MSS.368
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Printed Ephemera
  - Subseries B: Print Ephemera
    - Alice in Wonderland Illustrated Stationery for Children, 1961 (Box 36, Item 4)
    - Alice in Wonderland Illustrated Stationery for Children, 1961 (Box 36, Item 5)
    - Alice in Wonderland Correspondence Notes; 14 Notes with 14 Envelopes 7 Different Designs, [Undated] (Box 36, Item 6)
    - Alice in Wonderland Correspondence Notes; 14 Notes with 14 Envelopes 7 Different Designs, [Undated] (Box 36, Item 7)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland; 18 Sheets of notepaper 12 Envelopes, 1951 (Box 78, Item 3)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland; 18 Sheets of notepaper 12 Envelopes, 1951 (Box 78, Item 4)
    - White Rabbit Notebook, [Undated] (Box 36, Item 14)
    - How Alice Grew Tall Notebook, [Undated] (Box 36, Item 15)
    - Arthur Rackham Notecards, [Undated] (Box 36, Item 16)
      6 of his paintings from Alice in Wonderland in full color mounted on fine paper with matching envelopes.
    - Alice in Wonderland Notecards, 1980 (Box 36, Item 17)
      6 note cards boxed with color illustrations by M.L. Kirk, Charles Robinson, John Tenniel and Arthur Rackham. Boxed with inaccurate statement that 6 different artists are represented.
    - Alice in Wonderland Notecards, [Undated] (Box 36, Item 18)
    - Alice in Wonderland Notecards, [Undated] (Box 36, Item 19)
    - Arthur Rackham Notecards, [Undated] (Box 36, Item 20)
      6 of Rackham illustrations from Alice's Adventures in Wonderland in full color mounted on paper with matching envelopes.
    - Hallmark Alice in Wonderland Party Invitations, [Undated] (Box 36, Item 21)
      8 Hallmark Party Invitations. Invitations are pop-ups.
    - Alice in Wonderland Notecards, [Undated] (Box 36, Item 23)
      5 Alice in Wonderland Notecards with Christmas/New Year's greetings. Titles include: The Arm in the Window, Who Stole the Tarts?, The Dodo Presents Alice with Her Prize, Oh Dear! Oh Dear! I shall be too Late, and The Baby Turns into a Pig.
    - Hallmark Alice in Wonderland Party Invitations, [Undated] (Box 36, Item 24)
    - Alice in Wonderland Bookplates, [Undated] (Box 36, Item 25)
    - Set of 11 Alice Notecards by Kramer Designs, 1967 (Box 36, Item 32)
    - Alice in Wonderland Stationary, [Undated] (Box 36, Item 33)
    - Alice in Wonderland Advertisements, [Undated] (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Alice in Wonderland Advertising Pamphlets, 1950-1970 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland Bookmarks, [Undated] (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Alice in Wonderland Cocktail Napkins, [Undated] (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Alice in Wonderland Color and Re-Color Cards, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Alice in Wonderland Ephemera, [Undated] (Box 46, Folder 6)
      1. Alice in Wonderland Political Cartoon/Pastiche of various scenes from the book, water-colored illustration, on the back are four photographs and the word 'Cribbage'. 2. Trial of the Knave of Hearts by Arthur Rackhelm. 3. Signature of John Tenniel, dated 1901. 4. Alice in Wonderland Proof. 5. The Sluggard, print and poem published in 1812.
      Dimensions: 1. 9"x11.25". 2. 10.5"x7.5".
    - Alice in Wonderland Exhibition Programs and Newsletters of the Lewis Carroll Society, 1970-2000 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Alice in Wonderland Greeting Card, [Undated] (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Alice in Wonderland Photographs, [Undated] (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Alice in Wonderland Postcards, [Undated] (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Alice in Wonderland Procter and Gamble Coupons, [1960] (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Alice in Wonderland Silhouettes, [Undated] (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Alice Print, 1914 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Chicago Sunday Tribune; Alice in Wonderland by Will Davidson, [Undated] (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Chicago Sunday Tribune; May 30, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Hand-Colored Carrollian Paper Cutouts, [Undated] (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Menu from the Restaurant the Walrus and the Carpenter, [Undated] (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - The Real Alice; a Photograph by Lewis Carroll, [1920] (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Script from the Play Alice in the Wonderland of Pooh, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Magazine Clipping, [1952] (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Walt Disney's Classics Calendar, 1982 (Box 48, Item 2)
    - Paper Shopping Bag with Alice Characters, [Undated] (Box 48, Item 5)
    - Paper Shopping Bag with Alice Characters, [Undated] (Box 48, Item 6)
    - Paper Shopping Bag with Alice Characters, [Undated] (Box 48, Item 7)
    - Japanese stationery, Undated (Box 75, Folder 3-4)
  - Subseries C: Posters
    - Bottle and Jug Advertisement, [Undated]
      Dimensions: 13"x10"
    - Bottle and Jug Advertisement, [Undated]
    - Bottle and Jug Advertisement, [Undated]
    - Bottle and Jug Advertisement, [Undated]
    - Cards Painting White Roses Red by Arthur Rackhelm, [Undated]
      Dimensions: 11.5"x10"
    - Cards Painting White Roses Red by Arthur Rackhelm, [Undated]
    - Alice timeline -- Howard Change, 2010 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Series VI: Photographs/Slides
  - Subseries A: Slides
    - Medley of Slides of Alice Events, [Undated] (Box 42, Item 1)
      Slides include images of Dr. Lall and his collection of Alice in Wonderland Ephemera, black and white photographs of Lewis Carroll and Alice Liddell, and stills from the 1951 Disney movie.
    - Slides of Dr. Lall Montgomery and His Carrollinian Display, [Undated] (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Subseries B: Photographs
    - Photos of Cast "Through the Looking Glass", [1970's] (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Photos of Cast "Through the Looking Glass", [1970's] (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Photo of Henry Street Playhouse Dance Company: The Lobster Quadrille, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      The Lobster Quadrille with Alice, the Gryphon, the Mock Turtle, snails, lobsters, etc. (And Whitings of course)
    - Photo of Henry Street Playhouse Dance Company: Alice with the Gryphon and Mock Turtle, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      Alice with Gryphon and Mock Turtle. A charming story-ballet for children. Imaginatively dance, costumed and choreographed delightfully.
    - Photos of Dartmouth Winter Carnival Snow Sculpture, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      T15 photographs of Alice in Wonderland snow/ice sculptures from the Dartmouth Winter Carnival, 1973. Titles include: Trucking with Alice, Toadledum and Toadledee, White Rabbit, Humpty Dumpty, Mad Hatter, Caterpillar and Toadstools, Walrus, King of Hearts, Cheshire Cat, Through a Frosted Looking Glass, Caterpillar and Toadstools, Cheshire Cat, Humpty Dumpty, Mad Hatter and Mad Hatter's Party.
    - Photos of Dr. Lall Montgomery and His Carrollinian Display, [Undated] (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Photos of Dr. Lall Montgomery and His Carrollinian Display, [Undated] (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Photos of Dr. Lall Montgomery and His Carrollinian Display, [Undated] (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Photos of Dr. Lall Montgomery and His Carrollinian Display, [Undated] (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Photo of the Mosaic Pavements at the National Gallery, North Gallery: Wonder, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Photo of the 1971 Indianapolis "500" Festival: "500" Float - Alice in Wonderland (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Series VII: Books/Magazines/Clippings/Newspapers
  - Subseries A: Clippings
    Folders in this subseries are arranged chronologically by date.
    - Articles 1920's-1930's, [1920-1939] (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Articles 1940-1945 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Articles 1940-1945 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Articles 1946-1949 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Articles 1946-1949 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Articles 1946-1949 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Articles 1946-1949 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Articles 1950-1953 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Articles 1950-1953 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Articles 1954-1959 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Articles 1960's, [1960-1969] (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Articles 1960's, [1960-1969] (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Articles 1970's, [1970-1979] (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Articles 1990's, [1990-1999] (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Articles Undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Subseries B: Punch Magazine
    Folders in this subseries are arranged alphabetically by title and chronologically within title.
    - Mr Punch's Victorian Era, Vol.1, 1887 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Mr Punch's Victorian Era, Vol.2, 1888 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Mr Punch's Victorian Era, Vol.3, 1888 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Punch's Almanack, January-December 1867 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Punch's Almanack, January-June 1874 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Punch's Almanack, January-July 1882 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Punch's Almanack, October 1892-July 1893 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Punch's Almanack, October 1894-April 1896 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Punch's Almanack, May 1896-June 1897 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Punch's Almanack, June-December 1899 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Punch's Almanack, January-June 1902 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Punch's Almanack, October-December 1906 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Punch's Almanack, January-June 1914 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Punch's Almanack, January-December 1921 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Punch's Almanack, January-June 1925 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Punch's Almanack, July-December 1928 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Punch Magazine, July 18, 1891 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Punch Magazine, October 8, 1892 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Punch Magazine, July 15, 1893 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Punch Magazine, June 24, 1895 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Punch Magazine, January 29, 1902 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Punch Magazine, December 4, 1907 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Punch Magazine, May 31, 1911 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Punch Magazine, April 17, 1912 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Punch Magazine, June 26, 1912 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Punch Magazine, October 16, 1912 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Punch Magazine, December 15, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Punch Magazine, March 16, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Punch Magazine, October 15, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Punch Magazine, June 30, 1926 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Punch Magazine, April 18, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Punch Magazine, February 20, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Punch Magazine, March 18, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Punch Magazine, July 29, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Punch Magazine, November 18, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Punch Magazine, March 7, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Punch Magazine, August 8, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Punch Magazine, October 8, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Punch Magazine, March 10, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Punch Magazine, March 24, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Punch Magazine, November 28, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Punch Magazine, January 18, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Punch Magazine, January 25, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Punch Magazine, February 1, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Punch Magazine, February 8, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Punch Magazine, February 15, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Punch Magazine, February 22, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Punch Magazine, March 1, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Punch Magazine, April 25, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Punch Magazine, August 8, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Punch Magazine, September 9, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Punch Magazine, December 9, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Punch Magazine, February 10, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Punch Magazine, February 24, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Punch Magazine, March 24, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Punch Magazine, May 5, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Punch Magazine, June 23, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Punch Magazine, August 11, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Punch Magazine, February 23, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Punch Magazine, January 27, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Punch Magazine, August 21, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Punch Magazine, March 7, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Punch Magazine, February 20, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Punch Magazine, March 18, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Subseries C: Magazines/Pamphlets
    - School Newspaper, March 1, 1898 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Columbia University, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland; 1943 Calendar (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Children's Book Digest; The Junior Reader's Companion, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Lilliput Magazine, June 1947 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Lilliput Magazine, August 1947 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Walt Disney Comic Book; Walt Disney's Unbirthday Party with Alice in Wonderland, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 6A)
    - Screen Stories Magazine, August, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Santa Claus Parade, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 7A)
      Contains a 6 page full color cartoon pastiche entitled Alice at the North Pole
    - Alden's Oxford Guide, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Gelman Solutions, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - The Doll Collector Magazine, January 1965 (Box 22, Folder 9A)
      Magazine has an article by Dr. Lall Montgomery "From Translating Lewis Carroll's Alice in Wonderland to Doll Collecting -- And How it Came About" describing his interests and origins in collecting Alice in Wonderland ephemera.
    - Children's Digest Magazine, October 1965 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, December 1965 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Journal of the Long Island Book Collections, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Behind the Looking Glass, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Julliard, Spring 1970 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Daresbury Parish Magazine, May 1970 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - French Paper Company; First Century 1871-1971 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - The Original Simple Crossword, May 1973 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Young People and the Law; What the Courts Have to Say, July 1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - The Appointment Book 1976, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Cricket; The Magazine for Children, April 1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Time Magazine, June 6, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Smithsonian Magazine, December 1977 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Croft Church Lewis Carroll Festival, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Alice in North Carrollina; Schedule of Events and Exhibition Notes for the Spring Meeting of the Lewis Carrol Society of North America, May 5, 6, 7, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Barry Moser Engagement Calendar for 1992 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Children's Literature Research Collection; The Image of the Child, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - The Grolier Club, January 1995 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - The Antiquarian Book Monthly, June 1998 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - The White Rabbit Tales; The Newsletter of the Lewis Carroll Society of Canada, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Books for the Bairns, [Undated] (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Further Magic of Lewis Carroll, [Undated] (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Subseries D: Books
    - Alice in Wonderland Happiness Story Book, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Alice in Wonderland Miniature Book Set, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      Three volume miniature book set with a volume of each: Pig and Pepper, Advice from a Caterpillar and the Walrus and the Carpent er. Silver Thimble Books, by Gordon Murray.
    - Alice in Wonderland Notebook, [Undated]; 6"x9" (Box 32, Folder 3)
      Hand-bound full leather notebook with tooled image of Alice and 'Drink Me' table on front cover. Blank pages for notes enclosed.
    - Alice in Wonderland Storybook; Illustrated by Tenniel, [Undated] (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland: A survey of Collector's Editions, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      Author: Wilson, Oliver
    - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland: An 1865 printing re-described and newly identified as the Publisher's "File Copy", 1990 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      Author: Goodcare, Selwyn H and Schiller, Justin G
    - Alice's Flip Book of the Cheshire Cat, June 1978 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Alternative Alice's, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      Author: Sigler, Carolyn (ed.)
    - A bibliography of the writings of Lewis Carroll, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      Author: Williams, Sidney Herbert
    - Catalogue of Photography, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      Author: The Cleveland Museum of Art
    - The Diaries of Lewis Carroll, Vol.1, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      Author: Green, Roger Lancelyn (ed.)
    - The Diaries of Lewis Carroll, Vol.2, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - The Diaries of Lewis Carroll, Vol.1, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - The Diaries of Lewis Carroll, Vol.2, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Dodgson at Auction 1893-1999 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      Author: Carlson, David and Eger, Jeffrey
    - An Exhibition from the Jon A. Lindseth Collection of C.L. Dodgson and Lewis Carroll, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      Author: The Grolier Club
    - Jabberwocky (miniature book), [Undated] (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Author: Carroll, Lewis
    - Lewis Carroll: An Annotated International Bibliography 1960-77, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Lewis Carroll and Alice 1832-1982 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Author: Cohen, Morton N
    - Lewis Carroll at Texas, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      Author: Taylor, Robert N
    - Lewis Carroll Bibliophile, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      Author: Stern, Jeffrey
    - The Lewis Carroll Handbook (Revised Edition), 1962 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      Author: Williams, Sidney Herbert and Madan, Falconer
    - The Lewis Carroll Handbook (Revised Edition), 1979 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Lewis Carroll Interviews & Recollections, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      Author: Cohen, Morton N (ed.)
    - Lewis Carroll Photographer, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      Author: Gernsheim, Helmut
    - Lewis Carroll Photographer, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Lewis Carroll's Alice, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      Author: Lovett, Charles C and Lovett, Stephanie B
    - Lewis Carroll's England, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      Author: Lovett, Charlie
    - The Mock Turtle's Song, [Undated] (Box 51, Folder 2)
      Author: Carroll, Lewis Illustrator: Rohlicek, Karel
    - The Monthly Packet, 1880-1881 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Obituaries of Lewis Carroll, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      Author: Imholtz Jr and August, A and Lovett, Charlie (ed.)
    - Proceedings of The Second International Lewis Carroll Conference, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      Author: Lovett, Charlie (ed.)
    - The Strand Magazine, Vol.15, January-June 1898 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - The Strand Magazine, Vol.16, July-December 1898 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - The Strand Magazine, Vol.21, January-June 1901 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Surprise Books; Alice in Wonderland, [Undated] (Box 51, Folder 9)
      Author: Lebeck, Oskar Illustrator: Beckett, Sheilah
    - Tales from Alice in Wonderland, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - A Tangled Tale, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Visages d'Alice, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      Author: Clerc, Cristiane
    - The Walrus and the Carpenter; From Through the Looking Glass by Lewis Carroll, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      Illustrator: Rohlicek, Karel
    - Walt Disney; Alice in White Rabbit's House, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse Cookbook; Favorite Recipes from Mickey and His Friends, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Alice Redux -- edited by Richard Peabody, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Subseries E: Activity Books
    - Alice in Wonderland; Color by Number with a Complete Story, [Undated] (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book, [Undated] (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book; Alice and Pink Flamingo, [Undated] (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book; Alice and the White Rabbit, [Undated] (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book; Alice and the White Rabbit, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book; Pictures by Sir John Tenniel, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Alice's Wonderland Coloring Book, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Alice in Wonderland; Easy to Read and Color, [Undated] (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - A Peep-Show Alice, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      Two miniature books, The Chess Show and Preface, arranged as a peep-show.
    - Storybook Mazes, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      23 mazes based on classic children's stories. Pictorial wraps: 60pp. Page 10 is a Wonderland maze with brief explanatory text and b/w illustrations by the author.
    - Storyland Favorites to Color, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Set of four coloring books including: The Blue Bird Coloring Book, Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book, The Hiawatha Coloring Book and the Hansel and Gretel Coloring Book.
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Paint Book, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - A Wonder Cut and Color Book; Alice in Wonderland, a Doll to Dress, [Undated] (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Wonderland Storytime Coloring Book, [Undated] (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Series VIII: Art
  - Alice and the White Rabbit Tile, undated (Box 27, Item 1)
    Square felt backed tile of Alice and the White Rabbit, hand painted
    Dimensions: 4" 7/16
  - Alice (Drink Me), [Undated] (Box 27, Item 2)
    Painted, framed glass image of Alice ("Drink Me")
    Dimensions: 5"x7"
  - Leaded Glass Hanging with Chain of Alice and Carrollian Characters, [Undated] (Box 27, Item 3)
    Circular colored glass
    Dimensions: 10.5" diameter
  - Alice Among the Flowers, [Undated] (Box 27, Item 4)
  - Hand-made Egg Shaped Ornament; Alice and the White Rabbit, [Undated] (Box 65)
  - Ostrich Egg Handpainted with Alice Characters, [Undated] (Box 65)
  - Alice and the White Rabbit eggshell mosaic, undated (Box 73)
    Artwork is a mosaic made out of colored eggshells
    Dimensions: 13" x 12"
- Series IX: Media
  This series consists of five boxes of sound discs. Disc dimensions are 12, 10, and 7 inch; disc speeds are 33 1/3, 45, and 78 rpm. There is also one box of media; items include video games, audio cd, VHS videocassettes, Viewmaster picture discs, and 8mm motion picture film.
  - Subseries A: Sound and Video Recordings/Computer Games/Films
    - Alice in Wonderland CBS Irwin Allen Productions, 1985 (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland Caedmon Tape, [Undated] (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland Children's Video Playground VHS, 1986 (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland: A Classic Software Fantasy, 1985 (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland Interactive Multi-Media CD-ROM, [Undated] (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland NBC Home Video VHS, 1999 (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland Through the Looking-Glass Apple Floppy Disc in Box, 1984 (Box 67)
    - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland, Musical VHS, 1972 (Box 67)
    - Dreamchild; the Enchanting Story of the Real Alice in Wonderland VHS, 1985 (Box 67)
    - Four Views of Alice VHS, 1982 (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland, GAF 21 Talking View-Master Reels, undated (Box 67)
    - Alice in Wonderland GAF 21 View-Master Stereo Pictures, 1952 (Box 67)
    - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland, The Wonderland Quadrilles audio cassettes in box, [Undated] (Box 67)
    - Pari Banu Jokes/Songs, [Undated] (Box 67)
    - Super 8 Alice in Wonderland, Black and White, Castle films, [Undated] (Box 67)
  - Subseries B: Vinyl Sound Discs
    - 5 Kiddie Favorite Stories by Rocking Horse Records, undated (Box 68)
    - Agnes in Wonderland, 1980 (Box 68)
    - Alice Au Pays Des Merveilles, undated (Box 68)
    - Alice In Wonderland, adapted and prduced by Douglas Cleverdon, an Argo Recording, 1958 (Box 68)
    - Alice in Wonderland on Decca Records, undated (Box 68)
    - Alice in Wonderland Original Songs, Junior Records INC, presents Wonderland Records for Children, 1951 (Box 68)
    - Alice in Wonderland Musical Drama with Jane Powell, 1947 (Box 68)
    - Alice in Wonderland Why the Sea is Salt, Let's Pretend Records, c.1970 (Box 68)
    - Alice in Wonderland Why the Sea is Salt, Let's Pretend Records, c.1970 (Box 68)
    - Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs and Alice in Wonderland, vocals by Frank Luther, undated (Box 68)
    - Cyril Ritchard Selections from Alice in Wonderland, 1960 (Box 68)
    - Ginger Rogers as Alice in Alice in Wonderland, 1949 (Box 68)